Finding Aid for the W.W. Robinson papers, ca. 1843-1972
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Writings: not in Hicks, but arranged according to Hicks bibliography.
  - Clipping from: Los Angeles Times., No date; Presumably follows previous article one week. (Box 48, Folder 30)
    [Series About Title Insurance] Dangers Seen in Documents - Miscellaneous items - Publication - Reality buyers often victims of dishonesty; reasons why papers may be worthless; county recorder unable to detect forgeries
  - Clipping from: Los Angeles Times., No date; Presumably follow previous article one week. (Box 48, Folder 31)
    [Series About Title Insurance] Policy of Title Form Analyzed - Miscellaneous items - Publication - Various types declared to give protection; demand of easter capital causes change; losses not listed provided for by contract
  - Clipping from: Los Angeles Times., No date; Presumably follow previous article one week. (Box 48, Folder 32)
    [Series About Title Insurance] Expert Defines Title Policies - Miscellaneous items - Publication - Various types explained by official; full coverage provided in some instance; insurance granted against mechanics' liens
  - Barker Bros. Building; etc., No date; F. 1 of 3. 8 leaves total. Typescript (carbon) with holograph corrections. Numbered in holograph by WWR: 3 - 10. Some marked "used" by WWR. (Box 48, Folder 33)
    [Los Angeles Examiner Series] Barker Bros. Building - Miscellaneous items - Manuscripts - Broadway Department Store; Security-First National Bank of Los Angeles, 5th and Spring Streets; Silverwood's corner, 6th and Broadway; Rosslyn Hotel; the Bradbury Building; Edison Building; Van Nuys Hotel
  - Examiner Building,; etc., No date; F. 2 of 3. 4 leaves total. Typescript (carbon) with holograph corrections. Numbered in holograph by WWR: 12, 14 - 15, 17. (Box 48, Folder 34)
    [Los Angeles Examiner Series] The May Department Store Corner - Miscellaneous items - Manuscripts - Security-First National Bank of Los Angeles (6th and Spring Street Office); Paramount Theatre (Northeast Corner 6th and Hill Streets); Union Bank Building (Northeast Corner 6th and Hill)
  - Glendale's air terminal; etc., No date; F. 3 of 3. 3 leaves total. Typescript (carbon) with holograph corrections. Same format as previous manuscripts, but unnumbered. Some marked "used" by WWR. (Box 48, Folder 35)
    [Los Angeles Examiner Series] Glendale's Air Terminal - Miscellaneous items - Manuscripts - Chain of title to Bank of Hollywood property at northeast corner of Hollywood Boulevard and Vine Street; Examiner Building - 11th and Broadway
  - Chain of title Hollywood Vine., No date; Typescript. Similar to previous manuscripts. (Box 48, Folder 36)
    [Los Angeles Examiner Series?] Chain of Title - Miscellaneous items - Manuscript - To property at south east corner of Hollywood Boulevard Vine Street
  - Glendale growth told etc. Clippings from: Los Angeles Examiner., No dates; Articles relate to previous manuscripts. (Box 48, Folder 37)
    [Los Angeles Examiner Series] Planes Trail Ox Carts - Miscellaneous items - Publications - Southland traffic evolution. Glendale growth told; Indian raids peril L.A.: council votes defense fund, days of 1851 recalled; 3000 dollars grows to billion and does it in mere 65 years! L.A. reality, of course!
  - Clipping from: Los Angeles Times., No date (Box 48, Folder 38)
    Los Angeles Times Series? Oxcart to Airplane Tells Valley Growth - Miscellaneous items - Publication -
  - The beginnings of Pershing Square; etc., 1929 May; 7 leaves. Typescript (carbon) with minor holograph corrections. (Box 48, Folder 39)
    [Los Angeles Examiner Series] The Beginning of Pershing Square - Miscellaneous items - Manuscripts - When possession gave title to downtown property; Making Nigger Alley respectable; Pershing Square in 1849; Where Spring Street got its name; Rejected Mexican titles
  - Spring St., back in 1849, called Calle Primavera; etc., 1929 May 4 and no date; [WWR note credited]. (Box 48, Folder 40)
    [Los Angeles Examiner Series] Spring St - Miscellaneous items - Publications - Back in 1849, called Calle Primavera; History of land grants told in early records; 17, 172 acres patented to Los Angeles in 1866
  - Jonathan Club site; Clippings from: Los Angeles Examiner., 1929 Aug 3 and no date (Box 48, Folder 41)
    The Day Before Yesterday and Day After Tomorrow? [Series] - Miscellaneous items - Publication - Jonathan Club site; The Guaranty Building; Van Nuys Building; Nadeau Hotel; The automobile Club corner; Security First National Bank; Northwest corner of Eighth and Spring; Bank of Hollywood
  - Churches and schools; etc. Clippings from: Los Angeles Examiner., 1930 Aug 9 and no date; At least 15 articles in this series; Jonathan Club corner is adapted from article in previous Examiner series. (Box 48, Folder 42)
    Lots Made Famous in Reality History - Miscellaneous items - Publication - A series of historical articles concerning downtown properties as written by W.W. Robinson of the Title Guarantee Trust Company. Churches and schools; [untitled: Pacific Mutual Building]; Sixth and Hill; Jonathan Club corner
  - In: Commercial and financial digest: magazine of business and investment., 1937 Mar; V. 9, no. 15, p. 15. (Box 48, Folder 43)
    About Title Insurance - Miscellaneous items - Publication.
  - Public land surveys., No date; 2 leaves. Typescript (carbon). (Box 48, Folder 44)
    Public Land Surveys - Miscellaneous items - Manuscript.
  - Clipping from: California real estate magazine., 1932 Bun (Box 48, Folder 45)
    Public Land Surveys - Miscellaneous items - Publication.
  - Untitled history of Title Insurance and Trust., No date; 3 leaves. Holograph. (Box 48, Folder 46)
    Land Title Insurance - Miscellaneous items - Manuscript material - The story of Title Insurance and Trust Company of Los Angeles
  - The story of Title Insurance and Trust Company., No date; 3 leaves. Typescript with holograph corrections. 50 years old added in WWR's hand above title. (Box 48, Folder 47)
  - The story of Title Insurance and Trust Company., No date; 3 leaves. Typescript (carbon) with holograph corrections. 2 cop. (Box 48, Folder 48)
  - The story of Title Insurance and Trust Company., No date; 2 leaves. Typescript with holograph corrections and holograph. 2nd leaf is layout sketch. (Box 48, Folder 49)
    Land Title Insurance - Miscellaneous items - Manuscript material - The story of Title Insurance and Trust Company
  - The story of Title Insurance and Trust Company., No date; 3 leaves. Typescript with extensive holograph corrections. (Box 48, Folder 50)
  - The story of Title Insurance and Trust Company., No date; 3 leaves. Typescript (carbon) 2 cop. (Box 48, Folder 51)
  - Going on fifty - two:., No date; 4 leaves. Typescript with holograph corrections. Add above: the story of Title Insurance and Trust Company of Los Angeles Primarily a retyping of previous history. (Box 48, Folder 52)
  - Going on fifty - two:., No date; Typescript (carbon) with minor holograph corrections. (Box 48, Folder 53)
  - Clipping from: American Right of Way Association news., 1945 Mar; P. 2 - 3. (Box 48, Folder 54)
    Land Title Insurance - Miscellaneous items - Publication - The story of Title Insurance and Trust Company of Los Angeles
  - Typescript (carbon) about El Camino Real., No date (Box 48, Folder 55)
    Highways and By-Ways in Rancho Days. 1947 - Miscellaneous items - Research material.
  - Highways and byways in rancho days., No date; 3 leaves. Typescript (carbon) with minor holograph corrections. (Box 48, Folder 56)
    Highways and By-Ways in Rancho Days - Miscellaneous items - Manuscript.
  - In: American Right of Way Association news., 1947 Mar; P. 7 - 9. (Box 48, Folder 57)
    Highways and By-Ways in Rancho Days. 1947 - Miscellaneous items - Publication.
  - In: LASCA leaves., 1951 Jul; Quarterly journal of the Los Angeles County and State Arboretum, a California Arboretum Foundation, Inc. publication, v. 1, no. 4, p. 26. (Box 48, Folder 58)
    Chain of Title for Rancho Santa Anita - Miscellaneous items - Publication.
  - WWR's notes., No date; 6 leaves. Holograph. (Box 48, Folder 59)
    Romance of Land Ownership in Fresno County - Miscellaneous items - Research material.
  - San Joaquin Abstract and Guaranty Company [history]., No date; Typescript and holograph. With WWR's notes. (Box 48, Folder 60)
  - Romance of land ownership in Fresno County., No date; 4 leaves. Typescript (carbon) with minor holograph corrections. (Box 48, Folder 61)
    Romance of Land Ownership in Fresno County - Miscellaneous items - Manuscript material.
  - Romance of land ownership in Fresno County., No date; 4 leaves. Typescript (carbon). Incorporates above changes. (Box 48, Folder 62)
  - Correspondence., 1955 Apr, Dec and 1956 Jan; 6 items, 6 pieces. (Box 48, Folder 63)
    Romance of Land Ownership in Fresno County - Miscellaneous items - Publication material.
  - WWR's notes., No date; 2 leaves. Holograph. Chain of title. (Box 48, Folder 64)
    The Story of Chavez Ravine - Miscellaneous items - Research material.
  - Newspaper clippings., 1951 (Box 48, Folder 65)
  - The story of Chavez Ravine., 1958?; 3 leaves. Typescript with extensive holograph corrections. (Box 48, Folder 66)
    The Story of Chavez Ravine - Miscellaneous items - Manuscript.
  - In: Escrow news letter., 1958 Jul; P. 1 and 4. [This issue edited by Joseph J. La Barbera]. (Box 48, Folder 67)
    The Story of Chavez Ravine - Miscellaneous items - Publication.
  - Clippings., 1958, 1961 - 1962 and no date; Ned Cronin (Los Angeles Times sports page, 1958 Bun 3) credits WWR with information about Chavez Ravine. (Box 48, Folder 68)
    The Story of Chavez Ravine - Miscellaneous items - Post - publication.
  - Correspondence with Carroll R. West., 1962 Feb; 2 items, 2 pcs. (Box 48, Folder 69)
  - Letter from William Bronson to Elora Drake, CHB., 1966 Jan 5; Photocopy. Speaks of WWR's being quoted in Cry California 1965 - 66 winter. (Box 48, Folder 70)
  - WWR quoted in: Cry California, the journal of California Tomorrow., 1965 - 66 winter; P. 2. (Box 48, Folder 71)
  - Clipping., 1961 Jul 26; Pt. 2, p. 6. (Box 48, Folder 72)
    Letter to the Los Angeles Times - Miscellaneous items - Publication.
  - In: The clamper,., 1965 Dec; v. 5 no. 6, p. 5. Cf. Hicks. (Box 48, Folder 73)
    The Supreme Grand Humbug has Sounded the Hewgag - Miscellaneous items - Publication - Lindley Bynum 1965
  - WWR's note., No date; 1 leaf. Holograph. (Box 48, Folder 74)
    Los Angeles - Miscellaneous items - Publication material - Portrait of an extraordinary city; by the editors of Sunset Books and Sunset magazine. Supervising editor: Paul C. Johnson Special consultants: Lawrence Clark Powell, W.W. Robinson
  - Letters., 1967 Oct and 1968 Mar; 2 items, 2 pcs. (Box 48, Folder 75)
  - Los Angeles., No date (Box 48, Folder 76)
    Los Angeles - Miscellaneous items - Publication - Portrait of an extraordinary city; by the editors of Sunset Books and Sunset magazine. Supervising editor: Paul C. Johnson Special consultants: Lawrence Clark Powell, W.W. Robinson
  - Letters., 1971 Sep - Oct; 2 items, 2 pcs. Thanking WWR; enclosing payment. (Box 48, Folder 77)
    Unknown Contribution. El Pueblo de Los Angeles Brochure - Miscellaneous items - Post - publication -
  - History of subdivision activity in Los Angeles County., No date; 4 leaves. Typescript (carbon). No publishing information. (Box 48, Folder 78)
    History of Subdivision Activity in Los Angeles County - Miscellaneous items - Manuscript.
- Writings: The Land and the People (history of T.I.T.).
  - Certificate of title., 1875 (Box 56, Folder 1)
    The Land and the People - Unpublished writings - Research material - sources.
  - Examination / certificates of title from various companies, e.g. Russell, Poor Radley., 1880, 1886 - 1887, 1889, 1898, etc (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Abstract from The Abstract and Title Insurance Company., 1887 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Certificate of title. Johnson, Borden Yorba., 1887 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Certificates of title., 1887 - 1889 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Old title documents donated 4/11/58 by George Gummerson., 1887 - 1928? (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Sample titles, etc., 1888, 1933 (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Letter from Roland A. Kloess, enclosing 1888 abstract., 1950 Dec (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Photostats of certificate of title no. 1 issued by L.A. Abstract Co. on 9/2/89., 1989 (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - Photostats, title order no. 1 and first orders and certificates under name of Title Insurance and Trust Co., No date (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - Order no. 1., 1931?; 1 leaf. Typescript. From: T.I. news 1931 Dec. By WWR?. (Box 56, Folder 11)
  - Early certificates sent by E.A. Gregory., 1889 - 1890; 1953 Jan. (Box 56, Folder 12)
  - Early deed, mortgage, etc., 1889 - 1910 (Box 56, Folder 13)
  - Certificate of title., 1891; Note by WWR: This shows W.J. Williams connections with Sargent prior to TG. (Box 56, Folder 14)
  - Certificate of title., 1892 (Box 56, Folder 15)
  - Samples of early certificates, escrow instructions, policies, etc. Historical material., 1895 - 1896 primarily; From an envelope so labeled. (Box 56, Folder 16)
  - Title Insurance and Trust Company limited certificate., 1897 (Box 56, Folder 17)
  - Samples of early trust deeds., 1897 (Box 56, Folder 18)
  - Purchase of Rancho Rincon de los Bueyes property., 1900 (Box 56, Folder 19)
  - Early title insurance forms., No date (Box 56, Folder 20)
  - Samples of checks and early checks., 1895, 1923, and no date (Box 56, Folder 21)
  - Original check for $1,000,000 executed T G T Co., 1895, 1923, and no date; In favor of Baldwin estate. Also copy used for advertising. (Box 56, Folder 22)
  - Payroll, signed by O.F. Brant. Monies signed for by: N.W. Thompson, etc., 1890 Dec; 1 leaf. Also envelope with note. On Los Angeles Abstract Co. letterhead. Also: envelope with note saying "This is the way we used to get our cash." Uncertain if goes with this item. (Box 56, Folder 23)
  - Letter from C.G. Harrison., 1851 Aug; 1 folded leaf. Holograph. (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Typescript copy (and carbon) of above letter., No date (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - [Statements by and about E.W. Sargent. Copies]., 1890, 1895, 1925 [originals]; 7 leaves total. With WWR's notes. 1 leaf. Holograph. Concern Sargent's ouster from Los Angeles Abstract Company, etc. (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Photostat copies of Sargent's 1890 letter. (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Incorporation document (unsigned)., 1893 (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Typed copies of incorporation documents., 1893 (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Incorporation. Newspaper clipping., 1943 (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - WWR's notes., No date; 1 leaf. Holograph. (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - Typed notes about shareholders' (?) meeting., 1895 (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - Letter from O.P. Clark., 1893; Photostat copies. (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - Typed excerpts from newspaper article., 1896; Also WWR's notes. 2 leaves. Holograph. (Box 57, Folder 11)
  - T.I. home guards [WWI]., No date; By Johnson, Ralph. Describe?. (Box 57, Folder 12)
  - Scrapbook pages and loose clippings., ca. 1928 - 1937 (Box 57, Folder 13)
  - Telegrams about closing during bank holiday., 1933 Mar (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - News release., 1943; 3 leaves. Typescript (carbon). (Box 57, Folder 15)
  - Federal housing acts. WWR's notes., No date; 3 leaves. Holograph. (Box 57, Folder 16)
  - Federal housing acts. Newspaper clippings., 1963 (Box 57, Folder 17)
  - Post - WWII business outlook., 1944; Mimeographed material, magazine. (Box 57, Folder 18)
  - Information - home office, Title Insurance and Trust Company., No date (Box 57, Folder 19)
  - Historical chart of Title Insurance and Trust Company; comp. by George A. Reimers., No date [after 1942]; Several copies, as well as later organization charts. (Box 57, Folder 20)
    The Land and the People - Unpublished writings - Research material - histories.
  - Brief history of the Los Angeles Abstract Company and early history of the Title Insurance and Trust Company and of the writer's connection therewith; by Will L. Ramsey., 1916; 23 leaves. Carbon typescript. (Box 57, Folder 21)
  - T.I. Cavalcade., 1940; Also WWR's notes. 3 leaves. Holograph. (Box 57, Folder 22)
  - T.I. Cavalcade., 1940; Printed program. (Box 57, Folder 23)
  - T.I. Cavalcade., 1940; Script. [41] leaves. Typescript (carbon). (Box 57, Folder 24)
  - T.I. Cavalcade., 1940; Script (another typing). 18 leaves. Typescript (carbon). (Box 57, Folder 25)
  - Untitled, beginning: The story of title insurance., 1941?; 3 leaves. (Box 57, Folder 26)
  - Letter and memos to / from M.B. Ogden., 1941 Jan - Feb, 1942 Dec (Box 57, Folder 27)
  - [Ogden M.B.] History of Title Insurance and Trust., 1942; 32 leaves. Typescript (carbon). (Box 57, Folder 28)
  - [Ogden, M.B.] History of Title Insurance and Trust., 1942; 60 leaves. Another copy. Leaves 42 - 60 only. (Box 57, Folder 29)
  - 50th anniversary? Untitled "cavalcade" script., No date; 11 leaves. Typescript. Seemingly incomplete. (Box 57, Folder 30)
  - Title Insurance and Trust Company celebrates 50th anniversary., No date; 2 leaves. Typescript (carbon). With minor holograph corrections in WWR's hand. (Box 57, Folder 31)
  - Reminders in connection with 50th anniversary T.I. T. Co., No date; 2 leaves. Typescript. Another copy. Typescript (carbon). (Box 57, Folder 32)
  - WWR's sketches for 50th anniversary advertisements., No date; 2 leaves. Holograph. (Box 57, Folder 33)
  - 60th anniversary. Newspaper clippings., 1952 - 1953 (Box 57, Folder 34)
  - Forty year history of title companies in Los Angeles, January 1887 - January 1927; by J.B. Webber., 1946; 9 leaves. Typescript (carbon). (Box 57, Folder 35)
  - Information on General Title Insurance Company., No date; With WWR's holograph notes: Duval, former employee of TI T Co. (Box 57, Folder 36)
  - No title., 1899; Photocopy. Article from Los Angeles Times. (Box 57, Folder 37)
    The Land and the People - Unpublished writings - Research material - annual reports.
  - No title., 1947 - 1952 (Box 57, Folder 38)
  - No title., 1953 - 1957 (Box 57, Folder 39)
  - No title., 1958 - 1962 (Box 57, Folder 40)
  - No title., 1963 - 1964 (Box 57, Folder 41)
  - The insuring of titles on property., No date; 2 leaves. Typescript (carbon). (Box 58, Folder 1)
    The Land and the People - Unpublished writings - Research material.
  - Insuring titles in land., No date; 7 leaves. Typescript with holograph corrections by WWR. (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - The business of insuring land titles., No date; 3 leaves with WWR's holograph corrections. Could be notes / outline for and lecture. (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Copy of Mr. H.W. O'Melveny's speech before the American Bar Convention 1935 meeting., No date; 4 leaves. Typescript. With minor holograph notation by WWR. (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - O'Melveny's speech., 1935; [7] leaves. Typescript. Also WWR's holograph notes. 1 leaf. Another typing of preceding remarks. (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Speech on working of title insurance; by W.W. Powell., 1921; 11 leaves. Typescript. (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Title insurance., No date; 2 leaves. Typescript. With WWR's note: From, apparently, a mag. article. (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Mexican land titles., No date; 14 leaves total. Holograph and typescript. Holograph notes in ____ with translations. (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - Torrens title. Articles, etc., 1943, 1947, and no date (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - What protection is title insurance; by Lawrence L. Otis., 1927 and 1946; 10 p. 2 copies. 21 leaves. Reprint of an article. The community property problem; an address by Mr. Charles H. Brock. (Box 58, Folder 10)
  - The community property problem; an address by Mr. Charles H. Brock., 1927; 21 p. (Box 58, Folder 11)
  - Outline of land titles. Pt. 3., 1949?; Various pagings. California Land Title Association. (Box 58, Folder 12)
  - Sources of title to land in California. Pt. 1., 1965; Various pagings. Los Angeles, Title Insurance and Trust. (Box 58, Folder 13)
  - What is your market value? by Henry A. Porter. Los Angeles, Title Insurance and Trust. Par value 98 cents., 1929; 14 p. (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Trust service brochures and pamphlets., 1924 - 1925, 1928, 1931, 1937, and 1945; Various titles. (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Probate brochures., No date (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Wills and deeds of trust, brochures from other companies., 1922, 1927, etc (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Tax brochures., No date (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Realty financing brochures., ca. 1960s (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - WWR's notes on derivation of word, etc., No date; 12 leaves. Holograph. (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - Promotion of the escrow department; by Allan Herrick., 1955 Apr 25 and no date; 6 leaves. Other typed notes on escrow. Letter from Herrick to WWR. (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - Brochures about escrow., ca. 1930 - 1940 (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - Brochures about escrow., 1960, 1962 (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - Copies of T.I.T.'s Escrow news letter, published as a service to the escrow men and women of California [4 issues]., 1962 Nov, 1963 Jan, 1964 Jan, 1965 Jul and 1969 Oct; Marked by WWR: 1964 and 1965. (Box 59, Folder 11)
  - T.I.T. escrow forms., No date (Box 59, Folder 12)
  - Escrow manual; by Claire Cammert., 1962 Jul; Various pagings. (Box 59, Folder 13)
  - Story of typical escrow currently handled at Title Insurance and Trust Company., No date; 3 leaves. Typescript Also: another copy. Typescript. Another copy. Carbon typescript. At head of title: Appendix. (Box 59, Folder 14)
  - Escrow ephemera, clippings., 1963 - 1964 (Box 59, Folder 15)
  - Subdivision clipping and statistics., 1950, 1963 (Box 59, Folder 16)
  - Subdivision information and procedure., No date; 6 leaves. Mimeograph. Also: WWR's notes. 1 leaf. Holograph. Mimeograph. Also 1 leaf WWR's holograph notes. (Box 59, Folder 17)
  - The mortgage money market; by Willis R. Bryant., 1956; 19 [3] leaves. Typescript (mimeograph). (Box 59, Folder 18)
  - Brochures from California Land Title Association., 1938, 1952, 1963, and no date; Includes: newsletter, invitation to open house for move to offices on Wilshire Boulevard. (Box 59, Folder 19)
  - Building and loan company brochures., 1929 - 1930, and no date (Box 59, Folder 20)
  - Aspects of title insurance. Newspaper clippings., 1949, 1962, 1965 (Box 59, Folder 21)
  - Map., 1936 Oct 10; For: 32nd annual California Real Estate Association convention; map of metropolitan Los Angeles tour; compliments of Title Guarantee and Trust. (Box 60, Folder 1)
    The Land and the People - Unpublished writings - Title Guarantee and Trust.
  - An outline of services for attorneys furnished by Title Guarantee and Trust Company., 1938; WWR not credited. (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Ti Guar tales., 1942 Nov; v. 5 no. 11. No mention of WWR. (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Illustration / floor plan. Clipping., No date (Box 60, Folder 4)
    The Land and the People - Unpublished writings - Title Guarantee Building (5th and Broadway).
  - Newspaper clipping., 1930 and no date (Box 60, Folder 5)
    The Land and the People - Unpublished writings - Title Guarantee and Trust Building (5th and Hill).
  - [Untitled copy from Los Angeles Times]., 1905?; 2 leaves. Holograph. (Box 60, Folder 6)
    The Land and the People - Unpublished writings - Title Insurance and Trust building, Franklin and New High Streets.
  - Tamm residence., No date; 1 leaf. Holograph. (Box 60, Folder 7)
    The Land and the People - Unpublished writings - Title Insurance and Trust Spring Street building.
  - 433 South Spring in the days when the street was a dusty thoroughfare., No date; 1 leaf. Typescript. (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - Printed invitation to open house., 1928 (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - Title Insurance Building., 1928?; 9 p. Illus. (Box 60, Folder 10)
  - WWR's notes., No date; 7 leaves. Holograph. (Box 60, Folder 11)
    The Land and the People - Unpublished writings - T.I. Foundation.